

CONTACT

931 394 402 francisco.tadeu.torres@gmail.com <u>LinkedIn</u> <u>Portfolio</u>

EDUCATION

Games Technology BSc (Hons) Kingston University, London Graduated: June 2018

LANGUAGES

English (Fluent)
Portuguese (Native)

SKILLS

C# & .NET

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

Unity
HTML, CSS
REGEX
Hugo
Git
Jira, Confluence, Bitbucket
Azure Blob Storage

UNITY SPECIFIC SKILLS:

iOS & Android apps VR and AR apps WebGL optimization Addressables URP Tool development

Francisco Torres

SENIOR GAME DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I am a Senior Game Developer and Team Leader with 6 years professional experience developing games and other apps with C# and Unity.

I am a skilled team manager. I pay close attention to detail and I value good communication with my team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

TEAM LEAD

FakeDoor | January 2024 - Present

- Started this position as a Senior Unity Developer but was promoted to Team Lead when my team grew.
- I oversee my <u>team's work</u>, manage our sprints in Jira, train and support our Junior members and develop core architectural code.
- Additionally, I write **Unity tools** to aid our 3D Team import their work into Unity.
- Conducted interviews and brought in new talent.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Arkadium | June 2022 - December 2023

- Worked on <u>Journey Match</u> from ideation to publication.
- Developed the game's <u>core gameplay loop</u>, <u>custom</u> <u>shaders</u>, and level editing tools.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER - IMMERSIVE TECH EXPERT

Axians | June 2021 - June 2022

- Advised on international projects regarding the best use of VR tech for education.
- Developed a Unity VR app on Oculus Quest to increase risk awareness in dangerous work environments.

LEAD GAME DEVELOPER

Digital Influx | October 2020 - January 2021

• WebGL educational <u>endless runner game</u> in Unity.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

1825 Arch. Viz. Studio | February 2019 - October 2020

 Software development using Python, C# and Unity for VR and AR business apps and <u>museum exhibits</u>.